nfsunlimited.net 2012-11-14

# NFSUnlimited.net - Need for Speed Most Wanted, Hot Pursuit, World, SHIFT and more - Privacy Policy

**NFS Unlimited** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our  commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [NFS Unlimited](http://www.nfsunlimited.net/)

### Advertisers

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

### Personal Information

This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted.

Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes.

### External Links

This site contains links to other sites. **NFS Unlimited** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

### Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:  

webmaster at nfsunlimited dot net
